HELLO, TWENTY - WONHEE
Hello.
DON'T FORGET TO CLOSE THE DOOR
Good morning.
- Can you guess what you'll be doing?
- Well...
I suppose...
A mukbang show?
I'm ready for that.
BAGGY SHIRT
You're actually hitting a club.
That would be a first for me.
I'm not sure you're dressed for clubbing.
But we all know what's really going on.
WE'RE FIVE EPISODES IN
As you know, we're visiting a boxing gym.
EPISODE 5: BOXING
IS THIS A PREVIEW?
I know a few moves.
A MUST FOR 20-YEAR-OLDS:
BUILD A HEALTHIER LIFE
IT'S BEST TO MAKE AN EFFORT
TO MAINTAIN OVERALL WELL-BEING
WHERE IS OUR 20-YEAR-OLD VISITING
TO GET STARTED IN THIS JOURNEY?
TODAY'S LOCATION:
BOXING GYM
Today's girlie is a big name.
Of course, she's a star among stars.
She's got rizz from head to toe.
COME ALONG, WONHEE
I'm far from a boxer.
Here it is.
So this is it.
Patricia.
Wonhee!
EPISODE 5 GIRLIE
PATRICIA
- Hello.
BOUNCY
This is painfully awkward.
SO AWKWARD
How did you know?
It's so awkward.
I didn't know you trained here.
Oh, well...
ALMOST FELL
Why am I already out of breath?
LAUGHS OUT LOUD
What brings you here?
People in their 20s are
really into wellness these days.
THAT'S TRUE
So I wanted
to build both my body and mind.
And what better way than boxing?
How old are you exactly?
- I just turned 20.
- You're 20?
Yes.
- Now that I'm no longer a teenager,
- Incredible.
- I feel easily drained.
- They want us over here.
I'm so sorry!
I thought this was the center.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME
- So you turned 20?
- Yeah.
Gosh, you're just a baby.
I'm 25 this year.
Come on, that's still young.
No, I just told you I'm 25!
What was turning 20 like for you?
I'd been waiting for that day
since I was 19.
So you were one of the cuties going,
"I'm 20 now!"
I was like, "I can't wait!"
I was excited not to be stuck
in a uniform every day.
I wanted the freedom to choose
whatever I wanted to wear.
And I couldn't wait
to be done with school.
Getting to school by 8:30 a.m. every day
- is pretty rough.
- It's tough.
After I turned 20...
How do I put this?
The world felt completely different.
- Were you that excited?
- "I'm legal now.
- No one can mess with me now."
- So cute.
- "I'm legal now."
- "No one can touch me."
What was the first thing you did
once you became an adult?
What did I do first?
I think I tried alcohol
for the first time.
I wanted to know what soju tasted like.
Everyone makes that "ahh" sound
when they drink.
- That sparked my curiosity.
- I see.
I threw it all out after one sip.
- Me too.
- I emptied the bottle.
Seriously, I wanted to exclaim
like everyone else.
- Just for show, you know.
- Okay.
But I almost spat it out.
Let's go.
FIRST TASTE OF SOJU IN EPISODE 1,
GIRLIE'S NIGHT
Jeez.
BAD MEMORY
It literally tastes like an alcohol swab.
People say it's sweet,
but don't fall for that.
It's not sweet.
In fact, it's bitter.
Downright awful.
We're at a boxing gym, right?
Everyone's working hard
to build a healthier life.
What kind of exercise are you into?
Just call me a generous donor.
- To your gym?
- Yes, exactly.
My brother, Jonathan,
keeps calling me a donor
like it's a compliment.
- Is that a compliment, though?
- Sure.
For what it's worth,
now that I'm a bit older,
I realize I need to work out
to stay in shape.
Now that my teenage days are over,
I feel the same need.
You're so...
I mean, I'm 25.
WHAT IS SHE SAYING?
Have you tried boxing before?
Actually, no.
- Is it your first time?
- Have you tried it before?
Not at all.
- I thought you had.
- Are we both newbies?
At least one of us
- should know how it goes.
- Wait.
- You had the look of a boxer.
- I just--
- I mean, look at these shoes.
- I just threw them on
without thinking about the outfit.
- Weren't you punching the sandbag?
- Just some moves
- I picked up from dealing with Jonathan.
- I get it.
- Fake boxing.
- Just going through the motions.
Are you a decent fighter?
- To be honest...
- Are you any good?
- I'm not bad.
- Really?
Then again,
an older brother will take you there.
Even as a little girl,
I received training constantly.
Have you ever beaten him?
Of course not.
Not at all, but I have a story.
When I was in elementary school,
Jonathan punched me.
How mean. Why would he do that to you?
Looking back, I did cross the line.
- Still.
- I spat into his milk tea.
A LITTLE TOO EXTRA
I probably deserved it.
Are you okay?
FAINT
I spat in his drink.
I made fun of him, too.
Jonathan warned me,
"Cross the line one more time,
and I'll beat you up."
- But I--
- Did you make fun of him again?
I was like, "Hit me if you can."
I kept teasing him for a few seconds
until he actually hit me.
He threw a punch.
- But I was stubborn.
- That must've hurt.
- You played it cool?
- I went, "That didn't hurt."
- But after that,
- "You call it a punch?"
- you went to your room and cried?
- I didn't make it to my room.
It only took me ten seconds
- before I started crying.
- You cried?
WAILING
I cried my eyes out.
I FEEL YOU 100%
That's why my face is asymmetrical.
WHAT A SAD STORY
Is he a few years older than you?
By three years?
- He's older by two years.
- Right.
My brother and I are just a year apart.
- Really?
- So growing up,
we were about the same size
when we were little.
- Really?
- So if I gave it my all,
we were evenly matched.
But when we started middle school,
I couldn't beat him.
Do siblings fight a lot
when they're only one year apart?
You have no idea.
What did you fight over?
Things like ice cream and...
That's cute.
We fought over the remote control.
After school,
I had to rush home
to grab the remote first.
You get it, right?
- You're so brilliant.
- I'd be praying
for my homeroom teacher to dismiss us.
An absolute strategist.
When the teacher dismissed us,
I grabbed my indoor shoes bag
- and raced home.
- Did Jonathan also run?
Even now, I have to get home early
because he gave me a curfew.
- What's wrong with him?
- I know.
- He's unbelievable.
- I don't get what's gotten into him.
A 25-year-old can take care of herself.
I know, right?
I'm 25, for crying out loud.
Can you believe
I have to worry about curfew?
It's unusual for a brother
to give you a curfew.
He must really care about you.
I'm not sure if it's a good thing.
- Hello.
NO MORE CHIT-CHAT, THE COACH IS HERE
- Goodness, hello.
ESPECIALLY POLITE
Hello, Coach.
I'll be helping you
with your training today.
My name is Choi Jae-doo.
It's nice to meet you.
Coach Choi Ja-doo.
Wait, really? That's a cute name.
- That's your name, right?
- Do you know the cartoon?
- "Hey, Ja-doo."
- It's Jae-doo.
- Sorry?
- My apologies.
- Patricia.
SORRY
- I swear I heard "Choi Ja-doo."
- How could you?
- Sorry, the headband's covering my ears.
- Patricia.
I'm sorry.
OFFICIAL APOLOGY
- It muffled the sound.
- I get it.
I see you're both wearing boxing shoes.
WONHEE IS BAREFOOT
Can I get a pair, too?
About the shoes.
I didn't realize
there were shoes for boxing.
It's my first time seeing them.
- Same here.
- Oh, so the shoes...
Boxing is an indoor sport,
- there are shoe regulations for matches.
- Really?
Dang, I look legit.
- You know...
- Yes?
Your brother, Jonathan...
I'm a big fan of his videos.
You're with Patricia, though.
- But I'm Patricia.
- Of course.
As for compliments to Jonathan,
you can tell him
when you see him in person.
FLUSTERED
Oh, sure. It's just...
Am I his messenger now?
I just wanted to say I'm his fan.
- They have great chemistry.
- Exactly.
I also enjoyed Screening Humanity.
Right, their episode was great.
Of all the things to watch...
Just kidding.
- You're really...
- Yes?
TWO THUMBS UP
My gosh, Coach.
Your laugh, Patricia.
Your laugh is something else.
It's so clear and loud.
You can almost break
the sound down to syllables.
It's funny how we're all talking
about different subjects.
JONATHAN, PATRICIA'S LAUGH,
COACH'S THUMBS-UP
- Can you handle all this energy?
- Sure.
EMBARRASSED TWO THUMBS-UP
You like it?
Totally.
HAHAHA
I don't know why this is so funny.
Why are you this funny?
- Can we get started?
- Oh, sure.
- Do you need more time?
- Let's stop here.
- Let's do this.
- All right.
- We'll get started.
Before we begin,
- we'll do a warm-up.
- Yes, sir.
For starters, stand up straight.
Stretch out your glutes.
Knee up high.
We'll do an eight-count stretch.
One, two, three, four.
- This isn't so bad.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
- Switch feet.
- Wait.
You said "eight-count" in English,
then counted in Korean.
I was ready to count in English,
but he started in Korean.
It was almost...
- One, two, three, four.
- Let's just stretch.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Great.
Next, we're going to work on our quads.
Bend your knee and hold the position.
The other leg has to keep you grounded.
One, two, three, four.
- It's not so bad so far.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
THEY CONTINUE ON
TO STRETCH THOROUGHLY
Okay, then.
As you inhale, expand your chest.
DEEP BREATH IN
As you exhale, relax.
One more time.
HAHAHA
Exhale.
Good job. Well done, everyone.
We'll stretch out our hamstrings.
ONE MORE TIME
- Okay, I'll be quiet.
- Bring your feet...
This is harder than I thought.
So moving on...
Sorry.
- May I continue?
- You've got this!
- Let's go, Ja-doo.
- Bring your feet together.
Bring one foot forward and stretch.
Like this?
SO SEXY
- Am I doing this right?
- Oh, well...
Our goal is to stretch out
the muscles behind your thigh.
- I get it.
- It's working now.
Do I say "yum" when I feel the burn?
What?
INQUISITIVE 20-YEAR-OLD
Twentysomethings are always curious.
Don't panic.
- Don't people say that at the gym?
- They do.
- Whenever they feel it, "Yum!"
- "Yum!"
WHEN THE MUSCLES KICK IN
Gym rats go, "Yum!"
"Yum!"
Let's move on.
OVERWHELMED
SAD
One, two, three, four.
- I hope he doesn't run away.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
The other side.
- One, two, three, four.
- Yum.
...seven, eight.
I'm hot and exhausted already.
That was a lot. Can we take five?
- Let's get some water.
- Today won't be easy.
That's a wrap on warm-up stretching.
- That was only the warm-up?
- Right.
- When do we start punching?
- With every workout,
you need a proper warm-up.
Why don't we get started
with a few jumping jacks?
We'll do just 20.
"Just 20"?
- Understood.
- One more thing.
Jump high and clap overhead.
- Okay.
- High?
What if we hit the ceiling?
- What happens then?
- If you get hurt,
we can cover any cost
with the gym's insurance.
What about my pain?
I wasn't asking about damage to the gym.
- I'd be hurt.
- Oh, I get it.
- Why don't you try jumping?
- I think I can reach it.
One, two, three!
TOUCHED
- Let's give it a go.
- Okay.
Ready, go.
- One, two, three.
- One!
- Two!
- One, two, three.
- Why aren't you doing it with us?
- Come on!
- One, two, three.
- Five!
- Seven!
- One, two, three.
- Eight!
- Let's keep going.
- Nine!
- One, two, three.
- Ten!
CHEATING
- One, two, three.
- I'm tired!
- Sixteen!
- One, two, three.
- Twenty!
Great job.
MY EARS HURT
Coach...
THUMBS-UP AT LAST
You did an excellent job.
ABOUT TO THROW UP
WAIT, YOUR TOP
Oh, thank you.
Was that too much for you?
- No, we're fine.
- Are you?
We're just catching our breath.
We're taking a break, that's all.
JUST A LITTLE BREAK
Next up are burpees.
Burpees? I've never heard of it.
Let me show you how it's done.
Put your hands on the floor
and kick your feet back.
Come back up and jump. That's one rep.
- Okay.
- Would you like to see again?
- Yes, please.
- All right. One, two, three.
- You're good at this, Coach.
- One more time.
One, two, three.
YOU'RE THE BEST, COACH
So that's how it's done.
We've got this, right?
Let's just do six burpees
to get warmed up.
Are you ready?
- Yes!
- That's the spirit.
Ready, go.
- One, two, three. One!
- One!
- One, two, three. Two!
- Two!
TWO ARE IN SYNC
Come on.
BUT PATRICIA ISN'T
- One, two, three. Five!
- Coach, please!
- One last time!
- Five!
One, two, three.
THE END
Good job, Patricia.
I jumped like a frog.
You were perfect. I saw your form.
- That wasn't easy.
- Right.
DOUBLE THUMBS-UP
Thanks for hanging in there.
So that was a simple warm-up exercise.
- Okay.
- "Simple"?
To check your stamina,
we'll try battle ropes.
- That?
- You mean this?
- Do we have to swing the ropes?
- Exactly.
I've never tried it.
Could you help, Coach Kim?
Are you also a coach?
He must be.
Hello, Coach.
ENTERS WITH BATTLE ROPES
Hello.
COACH KIM HYUN-GI
This tests explosive power
- more than endurance.
- I see.
Put as much power into it as you can.
With feet shoulder-width apart...
Okay.
Send the waves all the way to the end.
- All the way to...
- Like this.
WAVES
You're awesome, Coach!
All right.
- We'll time 30 seconds.
- What?
- Well, I mean...
- For his demo.
- The 30 seconds for the demo?
YAY
READS THE ROOM
How about 20 seconds for you?
PATRICIA IS HAPPY
Or 10 seconds?
- Good luck, Coach Kim!
- Let's see a demonstration.
- You could get hurt, so step back a bit.
- Step back.
Step back, everyone.
- You're putting pressure on him.
- Stay back for your safety.
THE PRESSURE IS ON
- So cool!
- He's rolled up his sleeves.
Ready, go.
ROPES RIPPLING VIGOROUSLY
Wow, so strong.
Keep it going. Just a bit harder.
Way to go.
More.
Keep the waves going.
- How much time is left?
- He has 13 seconds.
- Go, Coach Kim!
- Ten seconds now.
WE ARE CHEERING FOR YOU
GIVING IT EVERYTHING
- You're amazing.
- One.
Stop.
- Just wow.
- Incredible.
- Why are we tired?
- I don't know.
Even ten seconds looks hard.
It's your turn now.
As the older trainee today,
I'd like to volunteer...
Just ten seconds?
...to go after Wonhee.
- What?
- You can go first.
I SEE
Why don't you go first, Wonhee?
- I just--
- I'd like to go after Patricia
so I can watch and learn.
Is that right?
- Okay, I'll go first.
- Rock-paper-scissors?
GIRLIE GOES FIRST
We have a lot to cover,
- so I'll give you ten seconds.
- Got it.
FIRST CHALLENGER, PATRICIA
APPROXIMATELY 7.2KG
These are heavier than I thought.
Are you ready?
Do I just swing them?
Yes, alternate your arms like this.
Have fun with them.
GIGGLES
- Remember
- The ropes are pulling me.
- to send the waves all the way down.
- Got it.
Use your legs.
Oh, so I put my legs like this?
Engaging my legs.
Let's go.
Ready, go.
START
POWERED BY HER BATTLE CRY
Until the end.
Hang on, Coach!
- What on earth?
- One. There.
- You did great.
- This is just...
- It's terrible.
- Is it that bad?
Really? She says it's terrible.
How did you last 30 seconds?
We have high hopes for Wonhee.
- So heavy.
- You've got this!
- Okay.
- Good luck!
- Engage your legs.
- Legs engaged.
Swing them just once. Go.
Alternate your arms.
- Don't get dragged forward.
- Wonhee.
WILL SHE BE OKAY?
Just ten seconds. Ready, go.
START
- You're good.
- Keep it going.
- Make bigger waves.
- You're incredible.
Way to go, Wonhee!
- Three, two...
- Wow, you're on fire.
GUINEA PIG GOING FULL POWER
Okay, great job.
- I'm exhausted.
- Well done.
The funny thing is,
we haven't even begun the real thing.
It's only a warm-up.
RUNNING AWAY FROM REALITY
We'll get started on boxing.
Before we do, we'll wrap your hands.
ROCKY SOUNDTRACK
Are you familiar with hand wraps?
- I'll give you a rundown.
- Thank you.
The hand wraps protect
your knuckles and your wrists.
This is pretty cool.
I feel like an actual boxer.
Spread out your fingers like this.
- Okay.
- If it's too tight, it might hurt.
- You're all set.
- Thank you.
- There we go.
My nemesis during elementary school.
Jump rope.
I can do triple-unders.
- Seriously?
- Of course.
Each round of boxing
is a 3-minute sparring
and a 1-minute break.
So we'll try the same exercise
for three minutes
and take a one-minute break.
So we're jumping rope for 1 minute
and resting for 3?
- No, the opposite.
- Really?
AMAZED
That was so smooth.
I was trying to be clever.
When you hear the ding,
- start turning the rope.
- Right away?
Even if you trip, keep going.
- Can I do double-unders--
- Sure, feel free to try triple-unders.
Won't you cut down 30 seconds for that?
I'm afraid I can't.
- Understood.
- Let's get started. Ready.
START
Good.
This isn't easy.
How about a double-under, Wonhee?
- Me?
- Yes.
Oh, well...
- I'm building momentum. Give me a second.
- What?
BUILDING MOMENTUM
PERFECT DOUBLE-UNDERS
That's cool.
Thank you.
You're so cool.
I am, right?
No talking.
HEHE
High five. We're doing great.
- Just incredible.
- Skrr, skrr.
EXCHANGING COMPLIMENTS
You're something else.
It takes up more energy
than you might think.
Even young trainees want to take
a breather now and then.
So I have to be there to... Wait.
YOUNG TRAINEE TAKES A BREAK
Wonhee!
Pull it together, Wonhee.
You've got this!
Where are you, Wonhee?
ME?
How much longer?
- You have 1 minute and 27 seconds.
- Maybe 20 seconds?
We still have more to go.
- Get back to it.
- What the...
- Come on.
- Coach.
- Pick up the pace.
- It's been two minutes at least.
- You've got this.
- I've got this!
WRETCHES
I've got this.
With that,
we're down to the last minute.
At the 30-second mark,
try high-knee jump roping.
No way!
Sorry about that.
Sorry.
Coach.
This is just...
You'll hear the ding at 30 seconds.
- One.
- My ears are going.
Now, start the high-knee jump rope.
- Faster now.
- Again.
- You go, girl!
- Good job.
WONHEE PULLS IT OFF
Patricia's doing it, too. Great job.
Let's keep it going.
Final ten seconds. Come on.
Keep going. Seven...
...three, two, one.
COLLAPSING
There we go. Good job.
Come on, Coach!
We have a long way to go.
Take a sip of water.
HYDRATION BREAK
Boxing is a combat sport
between two opponents.
Let's learn the boxing stances.
- Stances?
- Yes.
- Place your feet shoulder-width apart.
- Okay.
Now, remember your dominant hand
and take your foot on that side back.
- Take it back.
- Hold the pose
and turn your body slightly to the side
to stand at an angle.
At an angle.
- This way.
- Okay.
- Do I step inside?
- Sure.
- Copy and paste.
- Exactly.
Like this?
Raise your heels. One more thing.
Relax the muscles around your knees
and make two thumbs-up.
After that,
fold your thumb down
along the side of your fist.
Along the side of my fist.
Keep your right fist back as your guard.
Place it next to your nose
and right cheekbone.
So shy.
HAHAHA
I feel so shy.
SIDE EFFECTS OF WORKING OUT
I'm losing my mind.
DRAINED
You two are...
COACH CHOI'S HALF-HEARTED THUMBS-UP
You're so fond of me, aren't you?
It's getting a little much.
Bring your left hand
to the outer end of your eyebrow.
Move it forward,
leaving about four fists of space.
Keep your left fist at your eye level.
Now, hold that pose
as we move on to footwork.
- First, we'll learn the front step.
- Front step.
Be careful. You got it.
You're good.
We'll also learn
how to shuffle back and forth
like a pendulum.
Let me point out
where people often go wrong.
While practicing your footwork,
- you start moving like this.
- So true!
FIXED-TORSO
CORRECT, WRONG
Hold the pose. Ready, go.
FRONT STEP PRACTICE
There we go.
Right, this is exactly
what you shouldn't be doing.
We'll be sparring later,
and if your steps are like this...
Her steps are worse than mine!
This is idol basics. Watch and learn.
It's a two-step.
Like this.
I'll show you a dance from our new song.
Let's keep it going.
Back and forth.
Great.
Face forward.
Imagine an opponent in front of you.
Let's move on to punches.
You're here to learn, so...
CONCERNED
Am I pushing them too hard?
- Not at all.
- Right?
You're not pushing us.
Not at all.
We're fine.
- Can you stand up, please?
- Sure.
Great.
I figured out why I'm so exhausted.
I had a late-night snack yesterday.
- That's bad.
- I was wondering
why my body felt so heavy.
- I had a fourth meal!
- What did you have?
I had a burger.
- It's sitting right here.
- It sure is.
The exercises they've been doing
are very challenging for beginners.
Our trainees here have been doing great.
- Thank you. Nice.
- The viewers at home shouldn't think
- that they're overreacting.
- Exactly.
ROAR
Try it yourself.
- Try it yourself!
- Come and try it.
Let's learn how to throw a jab.
- We're going to start throwing punches.
- I've heard of that.
CALM DOWN, PLEASE
All right.
To throw a jab, first raise your fists.
Fists are up.
Extend your fist forward,
then bring it back.
Let me point out a common mistake.
People trying to punch hard
often push their shoulder forward.
Never lose your balance.
When your whole arm moves...
You might go, "Stop it already."
You nailed it, Coach.
- That's exactly it.
- "Stop it."
That happens when you lose your balance.
Your shoulder moves
because you're trying too hard.
Enough, okay?
The key in boxing
- is even weight distribution.
- An even balance.
When throwing a punch,
turn your arm
so your knuckles land the hit.
- Knuckles.
- Now put your guard up.
Let me see you try it. Ready.
- To the front.
- Ready, go.
JAB PRACTICE
There you go.
Jab. Okay.
Your jab isn't reaching.
One more time.
One more.
One more. You're doing great,
- but your back foot is dragging.
- Really?
Because your balance is off,
your jabs can't reach the target.
- You're next, buddy.
- Yes?
He's calling me "buddy" now.
I'm tired!
Give it a go. Ready, go.
Her jab is next-level.
A whole new level.
I'm so jealous. Dang it.
I'm going to train, too.
COMPETITIVE MODE ACTIVATED
That was great,
but you made the common mistake
ONLY MOVING FROM THE HIPS DOWN
of shuffling your legs only.
Always remember to move your whole body.
You must remember that.
- Hold up your hand.
- All right.
- Let's go, buddy.
Ready, go.
NEW DETERMINATION
I can feel the difference.
- I'm doing better, right?
- You definitely improved.
- She's good.
- You've got a competitive spirit.
Great job.
Let's try a one-two combo.
WHAT IS THAT?
A one-two combo is
a jab followed by a straight.
Hold after throwing a jab.
There we go. Now, another key point.
Your back foot should turn outward.
Twist around and find a balance.
There you go.
- Move your back foot.
- But my left hand...
Just a bit more.
- To here?
- Exactly.
- Easy to find a balance?
- Yes.
You too, Patricia.
Next, turn your back foot
and throw a straight.
Pow. There we go.
Well done. Just one thing.
Your whole torso moves forward.
- That way, you lose your balance.
- Right.
Then you can't transition
into the next move.
After throwing a jab,
your body should stick to the center axis
and just twist it.
There you go. Marvelous.
Let me see you try the one-two combo.
- One last time.
- Okay.
This time, connect the moves
- into a one-two combo.
- All right.
Give me a one-two.
Coach?
When you say, "one-two," do we punch?
- Pow, pow. Got it?
- I get it now.
Teach us the rhythm.
PERFECTLY UNDERSTOOD NOW
Pow, pow.
Now.
- Pow, pow.
CONFIDENCE REGAINED
One more time.
- Pow, pow.
- Amazing.
I think you're ready for mitt training.
Coaches, please help them with the gloves.
We finally get gloves!
Gloves!
Who wants to go first?
- Go ahead, Wonhee. I went first earlier.
- Me?
Okay, I'm ready.
Assume your stance.
WONHEE IS READY
Can you set the timer to 2 minutes?
I don't think they can last 3.
That's true.
We'll train for two minutes.
Fair enough. He saw right through us.
- Your left hand should hit my left.
- My left hand...
- Jab.
- Good job.
Bring your right fist here.
- My right fist goes here.
- Right.
Let me see your one-two combo. Ready, go.
PERFECT FOOTWORK
Good job. She's a natural.
Gosh, Wonhee.
She's ready for a match.
I can take all of...
FEISTY PUNCHES
Who let loose a kitten here?
Let's see her try it.
Hit the buzzer.
- Good luck! You're amazing.
- I've got this!
- Ready. Take a bow.
- Wonhee!
PRE-FIGHT BOW
- Assume your stance.
- Oh, we bow first?
Practice your footwork.
Great.
A NEW FIRE IN HER EYES
- Just a jab.
- Just a jab?
Wait, the one-two combo is this.
DON'T FORGET THE ONE-TWO POW-POW
Shift your weight.
There. Finish with a back step.
- You're doing great.
- Do I step back after the jab?
Yes, that's because your jab
- will be followed--
- By a counter?
Right, they will counter.
I have to dodge right away.
SLIPPING AWAY
Exactly.
You can't hit me.
Like a cute little squirrel.
Let's get back to work!
Back and forth we go.
All right. Good job.
TURNING HER BACK FOOT
This isn't easy.
It's not as easy as practice.
It's harder when you have to keep moving.
Punching while standing still
and hitting a moving target
- are completely different.
- It's so much harder.
- Oops, I lost the rhythm.
- Yes, the rhythm.
- One, two. One.
So adorable.
- Get moving!
- One.
One, two, three.
Great job.
Okay, one last practice.
We'll finish with five reps.
One-two. Back step. One.
One-two. Back step. Two.
Let's do five of these.
Ready.
Ready, go.
One. Bring it in right away.
Two. Right away!
Three.
Four.
Five.
A NICE FINISH
PATRICIA IS NEXT
Hit the buzzer.
Now, shuffle back and forth.
Could you call it out in Korean?
"Forward!"
THE MOST RANDOM REQUEST
All right, sure.
- That's a first from a foreigner, right?
- Well, yes.
Thank you.
Let's move back and forth.
One.
Shuffle back and forth.
One-two.
Good.
She's strong.
One.
One-two.
When you move forward... Let's pause.
- Your torso is leaning forward.
- Yes.
Don't lose your balance.
Move your whole body forward together.
WITH RENEWED DETERMINATION
One.
FIST FORWARD, FOOT BACKWARD
My coordination is awful.
It can be very tricky.
Viewers might find...
Trust me, I'm not messing around.
It's really challenging.
You must be exhausted.
You're like an animated emoji.
So cute.
One.
One-two.
One more time. One-two.
- Nice job.
- One-two.
Same as Wonhee,
wrap it up with five one-two combos.
- Okay.
- Keep calling it out in Korean?
Yes.
- I'll keep giving orders in Korean.
- Got it.
You've got this. Ready.
I can do this!
Ready, go.
- One-two.
- One.
- One-two. Step back.
- Two.
- Three.
One-two.
Oh, no.
Maybe it was too much for you.
This is so embarrassing!
- Don't say that.
- Not at all. You just did your best.
Why don't you rest a bit on the side?
- Can I?
- You can observe for now.
Okay.
Watch and learn from the side.
All right, Wonhee.
- You'll learn how to throw a hook.
- Okay.
Think of it as a circular punch thrown
while staying balanced.
Aim for your opponent's temple.
Oh, no. I wanted to learn this one.
I have a target at home!
I'll show you the basic stance.
Take this stance. Look.
Turn with the second punch.
There you go. From that position,
swing your arm in an arc.
- "Shut it!"
- That's it.
That was great. Turn.
From that position,
swing your right hand, too.
Exactly.
That was good, but one thing.
Your torso is leaning forward.
Keep your balance while punching.
- Let's give it a go.
- Okay.
Double hook.
- Double hook.
- Double hook. Good.
- What do I do with my legs?
- You should
turn your back foot on "two."
Exactly.
Just like that, turn your left foot.
- Double...
- Right.
FOOTWORK MATCHES THE FISTS
Turn your right foot.
- Double hook.
- There you go.
- Just...
- Double hook.
- She's so cute.
- It's...
From where I'm looking,
- you look like a dancing penguin.
- Right.
THIS PENGUIN CAN BOX NOW
That's it.
- She just nailed it.
- Yes, totally.
Try again. Ready, go.
Double hook.
PERFECT FOOTWORK
Nicely done.
Let me check your progress with mitt work.
Let's step this way.
MORE SERIOUS NOW
Ready, go.
Double hook. You're doing so well.
- One more time.
- She's talented.
Double hook. Okay, that was nice.
RAW TALENT DISCOVERED
She's a natural.
I should stay put.
Let's wrap this up with ten sets
of one-two combo and double hook.
One-two, double hook.
Let's go.
- One-two, double hook.
She's good.
One-two, double hook.
Okay. Good job. One more time.
Three. One more time.
One-two, double hook.
Five. Hey!
One last time!
CHARISMATIC FINISH
Thank you, Wonhee.
- You're great.
- Totally.
You're really good at this.
MUFFLED APPLAUSE
Jabs feel a little playful
because they go like this.
But hooks make you look cool.
- It has big movements.
- You're right.
You're right. In an actual match,
when a hook hits you
right in the jaw or the temple...
You go down?
- Yes, you do.
- Really?
How bad is the injury?
I'd like to use it on my brother.
If you're using it on Jonathan...
I'd like to know the recovery window.
I'll tell you something more useful.
Throw a straight.
It's the punch you throw
as you twist your back foot.
- Like this?
- Add hooks, too.
A straight and a double hook.
Then he'll go down.
THANKS FOR THE GREAT TIP
- There you go.
- That's nice.
- I'll have to ask him to stand still.
- All right.
Now that you learned how to throw punches,
- let's go on to sparring.
- What?
Sparring? I'm so jealous.
Sparring? Who's my partner?
COACH JA-DOO VS WONHEE
Get in the ring, Wonhee.
FIGHTER ENTERS
ROOKIE BOXER
WONHEE
Oh, shoot.
You're making me anxious. Take it easy.
RIZZ OVERLOAD
Coach me from the sidelines, Patricia.
ONE-DAY COACH
PATRICIA
Hey, Coach. What should I do?
- You're going to win.
- Really?
- What do I do when I'm cornered?
- With your hooks...
- When you're cornered?
- How do I escape?
Just drop to the floor.
- Sink to the floor?
- That's it.
I'm going to do that.
- Or try acting cute.
- Randomly,
"Hey, that hurts."
- "It hurts."
- But keep this in mind.
- We're not backing down.
- That's right.
Don't go easy on him
just because he taught you the moves.
First off, I'll go over the rules.
Anywhere above the belt line is fair game.
The same goes for both sides.
But you can't hit your opponent
behind the neck or on the back.
When you hit, use your knuckles.
- The flat side here?
- Yes, you can only strike with that side.
- I'll use my left hand only.
- Okay.
GIVING WONHEE A HANDICAP
How long is a round?
A round usually lasts 3 minutes,
but ours will be 2 minutes.
Let's give it a go.
All right. Begin!
PRE-FIGHT BOW
Let's give it a go.
Glove touch.
Go ahead and hit me.
Hit me.
Good. There you go.
SWIFT PUNCHES
Hey, you're doing great.
You're doing great, Wonhee.
PAYBACK FOR THE WORKOUTS
REVENGE-FUELED JABS
Let's go, Wonhee!
FLUSTERED
Wow, you're really doing great.
UNEXPECTED JABS
Great job.
BACKS AWAY
Take a breather!
A SUDDEN WWE MOVE?
ONE-DAY COACH LOVES JABS
A SUDDEN HOOK
You're brilliant, Wonhee.
- He's going too easy on me.
- Not at all.
I'm fighting back.
What happened?
MOMMY!
Sorry, it's all for the show.
- Don't worry.
- It's purely for the show.
COACH CHOI GETS SHOWBIZ
There he goes.
Feel free to hit me.
I'll defend this time.
You can't, though.
Stay on offense.
RUTHLESS ATTACKER
You're doing great.
What's going on?
GUINEA PIG RUNS AWAY
Wonhee, you poor thing.
I'm exhausted.
- Come on.
- Wait.
- It's over.
- No.
- That bell means 30 seconds left.
- What? Oh, no.
Do I guard like this?
Yes, hold both arms like this.
Put up a guard like this.
Try blocking.
- There you go.
- I've got this.
What kind of opponent is that nice?
PULL IT TOGETHER, COACH
ROUND 1 OF THE SLUGFEST ENDS
You're great, Wonhee.
Just a second.
DOWN TO 30% HP
She's got a talent.
- She's very quick on the attack.
- Right?
MY GIRL HAS SKILLS
At the start...
SHORTEST 1 MINUTE BREAK EVER
- What was that?
- On your feet.
- That went by so fast.
- Come on.
- You've got this!
- Get up.
BUT I WANT TO REST
Jab with your left,
then throw a right straight.
A jab with my left.
A right straight.
That's it. You get it now.
She's picking it up so fast.
DEFENSE WORK REVIEW COMPLETE
All right, Wonhee.
You're on fire!
Just a bit more!
Now, give him a roundhouse kick!
Wait, wrong sport.
Wait, stop.
You can't do that.
My bad.
- Attack!
- Reach a bit further.
Hang on.
Our girl is drained.
- Go, Wonhee!
- Take deep breaths.
- Okay.
- You're doing great.
Give me all you've got
at the 30-second warning.
You're up for it, aren't you?
I'VE TRAINED FOR THIS MOMENT
SHE ENDURED BRUTAL TRAINING
TO LEAVE NO REGRETS
SHE'LL LEAVE IT ALL IN THE RING
SHE WON'T LET HER SUPPORTERS DOWN
We have chocolate milk.
Ready.
Final 30 seconds.
- Here we go.
- Let's go!
You're doing amazing.
Give me four punches.
PUSHING HARDER THAN EVER
Go for his side!
WONHEE ON OFFENSE
Go harder. You've got this!
10 SECONDS LEFT
You're almost there.
DRAWING ON EVERY LAST OUNCE
OF HER STRENGTH
That last move was fire. Kudos, Wonhee.
PUSHING HERSELF TO THE LIMIT
ROUND 2 ENDS
Glove touch.
SPARRING ENDS
TOWELS ARE READY
Come here, Wonhee.
Well done. Be proud of yourself.
Good work.
She's got it.
Coach Choi was going easy on me,
but I couldn't keep up.
Sparring for two rounds is no joke.
You might think, "Why is she so weak?"
But it's really exhausting.
I would drop to the floor and give up.
Amateur boxers fight
two two-minute rounds.
You're at that level.
A SEAL OF APPROVAL
Your punches are great, too.
- So...
- Thank you.
That concludes our mini game.
Tell us the winner.
The winner is...
Wonhee!
Congrats.
- Thank you.
- All right, Wonhee!
- You're amazing!
Coach!
I SHARE THIS HONOR WITH MY COACH
Gosh, she's so cool.
Why am I the one sweating?
Thank you for training us.
BOWS TO COACH CHOI
Thank you, Coach.
- Thank you, guys.
- I'm out of here.
TRAINING ENDS
What did you think about boxing?
ESPECIALLY DEEP SIGH
My eyes are tearing up.
Such a shame, right?
I had so much fun.
But I've always wanted to go on the ring.
You know what?
I think I'm cut out for this.
- I felt that, too.
- I had fun.
Coach Choi felt it, too.
- He could sense your talent.
- Because of my strength?
- He said you were on another level.
- Really?
- I could've been his star student.
- What a shame.
How was it for you?
I realized it's much harder
than I expected.
You did great for your first time.
We both did great.
- I think we make a great duo.
- You know what?
Maybe we should keep training here.
We can stay here.
- We'll take over.
- Like tyrants.
We can stay back.
We can keep training.
THE GIRLIES' BOXING GYM
Do you always spread
this much positive energy around?
- I think I am. I like that.
- That's so nice.
I like making others laugh.
It makes me happy
when people laugh at my jokes.
It makes me more talkative.
I guess I'm an attention seeker.
Am I using that right?
If I had to train alone with Coach Choi,
it would've been awkward.
Really?
- I'm shy around new people.
- You are?
Thanks to your energy,
- I had it so easy. I'm so grateful.
- Really?
- I'm glad to hear that.
- I can't thank you enough.
Still, you can't be full of energy
all the time.
When do I feel tired?
When the food coma hits.
Food coma is no joke.
My favorite thing is
eating well and taking a nap.
People think something's wrong with me
when I'm really just full.
How cute is that?
I can't really think of times
when I feel down.
Maybe you're just naturally cheerful.
You're like the sun.
- I'm very energetic.
- You're like a ray of sunshine.
A ray of sunshine?
You're like a ray of sunshine.
That's a good one.
MS. SUNSHINE
What's your secret to staying so positive?
Positive thinking.
- You make an effort to think that way.
- Yes, I do.
Are you seeing anyone?
No.
I'm not in a relationship.
I heard you once tried to ask out
Jonathan's friend.
- About that.
- Can I ask about it?
I talk about that story everywhere I go.
At this point,
I should print the story on a T-shirt.
I'll tell you how it happened.
When I was little,
I had a crush on this boy.
- And he was Jonathan's friend?
- Yes.
Oh, my.
Here's what happened.
I told him that I liked him.
You won't believe what happened next.
He transferred schools within a week.
I drove him away.
But that's not on you.
Right?
But Jonathan kept telling me
- how I was responsible for that.
- That's so mean.
There were about four of them.
I drove them all away.
- So there were multiple guys?
- Yes.
TOO MANY COINCIDENCES
He calls me a repeat offender.
Since that's the case,
it's easier to misunderstand,
but you couldn't have been
the deciding factor.
Their family finances or other issues
must've been involved,
not some schoolgirl's confession.
- Right? So--
- That can't have done it.
- None of it was on me.
- Of course not. Don't you worry.
Why are you comforting me?
Because Jonathan keeps blaming you.
I can relate.
I hear Jonathan keeps an eye
on your male friends.
I'm really curious, though.
- Mine doesn't.
- Is he the weird one?
- He is.
- Really?
Let's say I go out.
When he asks who I'm with,
I have to tell him.
Wait, I get it now.
You were never the reason.
Maybe Jonathan scared off
the guys you liked.
That's not it.
He keeps nagging
because he doesn't want
to lose his friends.
He's keeping an eye on me
so he won't lose more friends.
Do you get it now?
I didn't want to spell that out myself.
But that's the truth.
JONATHAN HAD HIS REASONS
That's so petty, though.
What's wrong with him?
You're really good at this.
Are you flirting with me?
Sure.
THAT WORKED
I saw your potential as a boxer today.
Are there any other sports
you'd like to try?
Boxing was something
I'd always wanted to try.
What was this called again?
- Climbing?
- Yes, climbing.
- I'm also interested.
- You are?
I want to try it,
but it scares me.
- In case you might fall?
- Yeah.
I have another favorite.
- Swimming. I love the water.
- Oh, really?
- Me too.
- I can't wait to go swimming again.
I sometimes book a hotel
just to use their swimming pool.
- Honestly--
- I can't swim, though.
Even after my debut, I went
to a community sports center for a swim.
I even wore fins.
You must be pretty good.
LIKE A MERMAID
All I can manage is this
while standing in the pool.
Basically, I just walk around.
JUST WALKING AROUND
I'd love to go swimming with you.
We're a match.
HERE'S MY WORKOUT BUDDY
I always ask this question
to all the guests on my show.
Do you have any advice for me
as I navigate my 20th year?
Experience as many different things
as you can.
Even small things.
- Like traveling alone?
- Or going to a café alone.
- I've never been to a café alone.
- Right?
You'll find a lot of things
you haven't tried before.
When I was 20...
Well...
I was busy working.
While I appreciated
all the opportunities I was given,
it kept me from trying new things.
You mostly gained
work-related experiences.
I never got to travel alone.
I can't even eat out alone.
- Even now?
- Yes.
- I've never tried it before.
- Really?
You'll be surprised to hear my list.
I've never traveled alone.
Some people go on solo trips, right?
- Hanging out with friends?
- Yes, I never got to experience that.
I think it's really important
to make time for yourself.
Just try things head-on.
- "Head-on"?
- Yeah.
I get very anxious about failure.
- Me too.
- It frightens me so much
that I always hesitate
before starting something new.
- Same.
- I see. So...
I'm still struggling with this,
but I think it's a good challenge
for people in their 20s.
I know it sounds odd, but you're
at a good age to learn to accept failures.
I believe failures build resiliency
and allow you to become stronger.
That's what I want to tell you.
I never got to do that.
BE STRONG, WONHEE
- That's so wise.
- I never got to do that.
Thank you for your amazing advice.
- Let's meet again--
- Huh?
- That's it for the day?
- Yes.
- Thank you for your kind words.
- Was that an interview?
Yes, thanks for your wisdom.
- No problem.
- Let's try a new sport next time.
I'd love that. Next time,
we can try swimming
and other sports together.
Thank you.
My gosh, Wonhee.
"DON'T BE AFRAID OF FAILURES
AND FACE CHALLENGES HEAD-ON"
NEXT EPISODE
Exhale.
FOLLOWER 1 WONHEE
EPISODE 6 GIRLIE
FOLLOWER 2 MIYEON
SIXTH ITEM ON WONHEE'S BUCKET LIST
TEMPLE STAY
THE QUIETEST SHOW EVER
END OF SILENCE
Half bow.
HESITATES
THE NEWBIE FOLLOWER KEEPS MISSING THE BEAT
SNAP
FUMBLES
RUSHING
HALTS, SNAP
JUST A SECOND... THAT WAS TOO FAST
What should I do
when I'm worried about the future?
THIS FOLLOWER IS FULLY IMMERSED
CRACKS UP
She's so serious.
TEMPLE STAY COMING SOON
Subtitle translation by Jeongwoo Kim